{
    "id": "b1999f6e42e24d4592a54a8f23b09a84",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He narrated the incident in ……………………….",
            "description": "In detail is the correct expression.",
            "answers": [
                "detail",
                "details"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………… see elephants or bears.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "rarely",
                "scarcely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It ……………………… rained this summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "rarely",
                "scarcely"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie was ………………………… interesting.",
            "description": "Too shows undesirable extremes.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ……………………….. an unexpected situation that I didn’t know how to respond.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The lecture was ………………………… boring.",
            "description": "Fairly is not used with negative ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "fairly",
                "quite"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel ……………………….. about it.",
            "description": "When a person feels sorry for something, they feel bad about it. ",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He behaved …………………………",
            "description": "Cowardly is an adjective. The adverb for this meaning is in a cowardly manner. ",
            "answers": [
                "coward",
                "cowardly",
                "in a cowardly manner"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a ………………………… smile.",
            "description": "Lovely is an adjective. It can modify the noun smile. ",
            "answers": [
                "love",
                "lovely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………… short.",
            "description": "Fairly is not used with negative ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "fairly",
                "quite",
                "rather"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is getting ……………………….. day by day.",
            "description": "When there is an idea of change, the comparative form is used. ",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………. resembles his father.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "close",
                "closely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}